No tricks, only treats.
Sing: Thriller is a animation, family, comedy film directed by Garth Jennings.
Buster Moon dreams up a star-studded spectacle set to Michael Jackson's "Thriller" in
this animated short featuring characters from the hit "Sing" films.
Buster Moon (voice), played by Matthew McConaughey.
Meena (voice), played by Tori Kelly.
Gunter (voice), played by Nick Kroll.
Ash (voice), played by Scarlett Johansson.
Johnny (voice), played by Taron Egerton.
Miss Crawly (voice), played by Garth Jennings.
Sing is an American media franchise created by Garth
Jennings and produced by Illumination.
It features the voice talents of Matthew McConaughey, Reese Witherspoon, Scarlett
Johansson, Nick Kroll, Taron Egerton, and Tori Kelly among others.
The first film, Sing, was released on December 21, 2016,
and received positive reviews from critics.
The second film, Sing 2, was released on December 22, 2021.
The series has grossed $1 billion worldwide.
The franchise takes place in a world inhabited by
talking, anthropomorphic animals.
It follows a koala named Buster Moon who, with the help of other animals,
puts on live theater shows that largely encompass singing.
The tone is lighthearted.